saveonlaptops.co.uk 2018-12-31

# Save on Laptops Privacy Policy

Box Ltd trading as SaveOnLaptops.co.uk are totally committed to protecting your privacy. We comply with the principles of the UK Data Protection Act 1998 and the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003 subsequently incorporating the EU Cookie Regulations of May 2011. We conform with the EU General Data Protection Regulation from 25 May 2018.

## **Overview:**

Box Ltd trading as SaveOnLaptops.co.uk. This privacy policy explains how we use any personal information we collect about you when you use our website [www.saveonlaptops.co.uk](http://www.saveonlaptops.co.uk/)

  * What information do we collect about you? 
  * How will we use the information about you? 
  * Marketing 
  * Access to your information and correction
  * Cookies
  * Other websites
  * Changes to our privacy policy
  * How to contact us 

## **What information do we collect about you?**

We collect information about you in order to process your order. That information will only be shared with other parties that are involved in the fulfilment of your order and deemed as a legitimate business interest. Marketing communications are consented separately.

The information we hold may include:

  * Your Name
  * Postal / Delivery Address’s (required to deliver your order)
  * Password (encrypted record of your password)
  * Phone / Mobile Number (For delivery issues / Updates)
  * Email Address (Used as your login to our site)
  * Tokenised Card Details (Limited details to aid future purchases and refunds)
  * IP Address (Used for Payment / Fraud Checks) 
  * Product Order / Invoice History (To fulfil any copy invoice’s / Warranty / Returns)

## **How will we use the information about you?**

The collected information about you is used to process your order, manage your account and aid any further communication regarding your order. For example a request for warranty / support with your purchase in the future / Product Review / Feedback.

In the processing of your order, we may be required to share your details with our approved third parties:

  * Couriers – To provide required tracking and order updates for your order
  * Finance / Payment Merchants – To complete the payment process for your order

If you also agree to marketing communications, we shall pass on your personal information to approved third parties to offer a range of services / offers. This choice is offered to you during the signup process. At any time you can unsubscribe from this by clicking here [www.saveonlaptops.co.uk/unsubscribe](http://www.saveonlaptops.co.uk/unsubscribe)

We will never collect sensitive information about you without your agreement. You have a right to ask for a copy of the information which we are holding and we will delete information or correct any inaccuracies for no charge as soon as you make the request.

We require all third parties to respect the security of your information and to treat it in accordance with the law. We do not allow our third-party service providers to use your information for their own purposes and only permit them to process your information data for specified purposes and in accordance with our instructions.

Data will only be released to other third parties (e.g. the police / HMRC) on request where there is a legal requirement for us to do so.

## **Marketing**

We would like to send you information about products and services of which may be of interest to you. This is a request made through our signup / order page and you have a right at any time to stop us from contacting you for marketing purposes. If you no longer wish to be contacted. Please click here. [www.saveonlaptops.co.uk/unsubscribe](http://www.saveonlaptops.co.uk/unsubscribe)

## **Customer Service / Product Reviews**

Box Ltd pride ourselves on our customer service and keen to get feedback and reviews on our products / service that you receive from Box Ltd. We share your order details ie the product purchased and only your email address to request a review on our service / product to help us improve our products and services in the future. 

## **Access to your information and correction**

You have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you. If you would like a copy of some or all of your personal information, please email or write to us at the following address. We want to make sure that your personal information is accurate and up to date. You may ask us to correct or remove information you think is inaccurate. Please email [data.protection@box.co.uk](mailto:data.protection@box.co.uk) with your request.

## **Cookies**

Cookies are text files placed on your computer to collect standard internet log information and visitor behaviour information. This information is used to track visitor use of the website and to compile statistical reports on website activity. For further information visit [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) or [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/). You can set your browser not to accept cookies and the above websites tell you how to remove cookies from your browser. However in a few cases some of our website features may not function as a result. If you would like advice and assistance here please contact at [data.protection@box.co.uk](mailto:data.protection@box.co.uk) and we will be happy to help.

## **Other websites**

Our website sometimes contains links to other websites. This privacy policy only applies to this website so when you link to other websites you should read their own privacy policies. 

## **Changes to our privacy policy**

We keep our privacy policy under regular review and we will place any updates on this web page. This privacy policy was last updated on 15/5/2018.

## **How to contact us**

Please contact us if you have any questions about our privacy policy or information we hold about you:   
By Email – [data.protection@box.co.uk](mailto:data.protection@box.co.uk)  
By Phone – 0121 202 0030  
By Letter – FAO Data Protection Officer, Box Ltd, First Avenue, Minworth, Sutton Coldfield, B76 1BA  
In Person - Box Ltd, First Avenue, Minworth, Sutton Coldfield, B76 1BA
